chillcreations.com 2014-02-13

# Privacy Policy & Disclaimer - Chill Creations

For our [refund policy](http://www.chillcreations.com/presale-questions#canigetarefund), please see the presale questions.

**Privacy policy**

This privacy policy sets out how Chill Creations uses and protects any information that you give Chill Creations when you use this website. When visiting www.chillcreations.com the site records on behalf of Chill Creations customer data for internal record keeping. Chill Creations may use the information to improve our products and services.

Chill Creations is committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

If you don’t want to receive information about activities, new products and services from Chill Creations, there is the option of securing your personal details. You can also at any time withdraw your permission to use your email address or details. You’ll also find in every send newsletter of Chill Creations or Joomla! Virtuemart iDEAL a unsubscribe link that you can click to indicate that you don’t want the information.

**Disclaimer**

While Chill Creations makes every effort to ensure that the content of this website is accurate, the website is provided “as is” and Chill Creations makes no representations or warranties in relation to the accuracy or completeness of the information found on it. While the content of www.chillcreations.com is provided with the utmost care and attention, we do not warrant that the information will always be up to date, be true and not misleading, or that this site will always (or ever) be available for use.

We do not warrant that the servers that make this website available will be error, virus or bug free and you accept that it is your responsibility to make adequate provision for protection against such threats. We recommend scanning any files before downloading.

Nothing on this website should be taken to constitute professional advice or a formal recommendation and we exclude all representations and warranties relating to the content and use of this site. In no event will Chill Creations be liable for any incidental, indirect, consequential or special damages of any kind, or any damages whatsoever, including, without limitation, those resulting from loss of profit, loss of contracts, goodwill, data, information, income, anticipated savings or business relationships, whether or not advised of the possibility of such damage, arising out of or in connection with the use of this website or any linked websites.
